<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Security on Anikah Fauzia</title>
    <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/tags/security/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Security on Anikah Fauzia</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/tags/security/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happens When You Install MSU Psexec!</title>
      <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-install-msu-psexec-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-install-msu-psexec-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you looking for a way to remotely manage your Windows computers? MSU Psexec is a powerful tool that allows you to do just that. It provides a secure, reliable way to manage remote machines and can be used to perform a variety of tasks such as software installation, system updates, and more.
Benefits of Installing MSU Psexec MSU Psexec provides a number of benefits for users. It allows you to perform tasks remotely, without having to physically access the computer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happens When You Unlock Your Facebook Account!</title>
      <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-unlock-your-facebook-account-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-unlock-your-facebook-account-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you one of the many people who have had their Facebook account locked? If so, then you may be wondering what happens when you unlock it. Well, we&amp;rsquo;re here to tell you that there are some amazing benefits to unlocking your Facebook account, and we&amp;rsquo;ll show you how to do it in just a few simple steps. So, keep reading to learn more about unlocking your Facebook account and all the great benefits that come with it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This One Simple Trick Will Keep Your Messages Secure With These SMS Lock Apps!</title>
      <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/this-one-simple-trick-will-keep-your-messages-secure-with-these-sms-lock-apps-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/this-one-simple-trick-will-keep-your-messages-secure-with-these-sms-lock-apps-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Do you want to keep your messages secure and private? With SMS lock apps, you can easily do just that!
What are SMS Lock Apps? SMS lock apps are mobile applications that allow users to lock their text messages. This means that only the user can access their messages, as they require a password or pattern to unlock them. This ensures that only the user can read and access their messages, making it a great way to keep your messages secure and private.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe How Easy It Is to Reset Your Admin Password in Windows!</title>
      <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-reset-your-admin-password-in-windows-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-reset-your-admin-password-in-windows-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Forgetting your Windows admin password can be a real pain! If you&amp;rsquo;ve ever been locked out of your own computer, you know how frustrating it can be. Fortunately, there are a few different methods you can use to reset your admin password in Windows. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explain the different ways you can reset your admin password in Windows, so you can take back control of your computer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discover the Secret to Never Being Locked Out of Your Facebook Account Again!</title>
      <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/discover-the-secret-to-never-being-locked-out-of-your-facebook-account-again-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/discover-the-secret-to-never-being-locked-out-of-your-facebook-account-again-/</guid>
      <description>I. Introduction Have you ever been locked out of your Facebook account? It can be incredibly frustrating to not be able to access your account and all of its content. Fortunately, there are steps you can take to ensure that you never get locked out again. In this blog post, we’ll discuss the reasons why you may be locked out of your Facebook account, as well as solutions for never being locked out again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happens When Network Discovery Is Turned Off!</title>
      <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-network-discovery-is-turned-off-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-network-discovery-is-turned-off-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Network discovery is a feature of many operating systems that allows a computer to detect and connect to other devices on a network. It is a useful tool for setting up networks, but there are times when it should be turned off. In this post, we&amp;rsquo;ll look at what happens when network discovery is turned off and whether it&amp;rsquo;s a good idea to do so.
Definition of Network Discovery Network discovery is a feature of many operating systems that allows a computer to detect and connect to other devices on a network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Simple Trick Will Help You Instantly Detect TPM Devices - You Won&#39;t Believe What Happens Next!</title>
      <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/this-simple-trick-will-help-you-instantly-detect-tpm-devices-you-won-t-believe-what-happens-next-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/this-simple-trick-will-help-you-instantly-detect-tpm-devices-you-won-t-believe-what-happens-next-/</guid>
      <description>What are TPM Devices and Why Should You Care? TPM (Trusted Platform Module) devices are specialized hardware modules that provide an extra layer of security for computers and other devices. TPMs are used to securely store cryptographic keys, passwords, and digital certificates. They are also used to authenticate hardware devices, ensuring that only authorized users can access them.
In today’s world, where cyberattacks are becoming more and more sophisticated, it is important to ensure that only authorized users can access sensitive data and hardware.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This One Simple Trick Will Reset Your Windows Password Instantly!</title>
      <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/this-one-simple-trick-will-reset-your-windows-password-instantly-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/this-one-simple-trick-will-reset-your-windows-password-instantly-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you stuck trying to reset your Windows password? Have you tried every password reset trick you know, but still can&amp;rsquo;t get into your computer? Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, there is a simple trick that will reset your Windows password instantly.
Overview of the Topic Forgetting your Windows password can be a frustrating experience. You may have tried all the usual methods of resetting your password, such as using a password reset disk or using a third-party password recovery program, but still had no luck getting into your computer.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
