<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Data Storage on Anikah Fauzia</title>
    <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/tags/data-storage/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Data Storage on Anikah Fauzia</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/tags/data-storage/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>This Simple Command Could Free Up Tons of Space on Your Computer!</title>
      <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/this-simple-command-could-free-up-tons-of-space-on-your-computer-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/this-simple-command-could-free-up-tons-of-space-on-your-computer-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to a Simple Command That Could Free Up Tons of Space on Your Computer Are you running out of storage space on your computer? If so, you&amp;rsquo;re not alone. Many people struggle to keep their computer&amp;rsquo;s storage space from becoming cluttered and full. Fortunately, there&amp;rsquo;s an easy command you can use to free up tons of space on your computer.
What is the Command? The command is called &amp;ldquo;Disk Cleanup&amp;rdquo; and it is part of the Windows operating system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happened When I Tried to Use My Internal HDD as an External!</title>
      <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-when-i-tried-to-use-my-internal-hdd-as-an-external-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-when-i-tried-to-use-my-internal-hdd-as-an-external-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Sometimes, it can be difficult to find the right solution for your storage needs. When I recently ran out of space on my laptop, I decided to try and use my internal hard drive as an external. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t sure if it would work, but I was determined to give it a try.
Background Information I had a 500GB internal hard drive that I had been using for a few years, but I had recently filled it up with photos, music, and other data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discover the Secret to Removing ShadowStorage and Free Up Space Now!</title>
      <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/discover-the-secret-to-removing-shadowstorage-and-free-up-space-now-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/discover-the-secret-to-removing-shadowstorage-and-free-up-space-now-/</guid>
      <description>Discover the Secret to Removing ShadowStorage and Free Up Space Now! ShadowStorage is a feature of the Windows operating system that stores data about changes made to your computer over time. It allows you to restore your computer to a previous version if something goes wrong. However, ShadowStorage can also take up a lot of disk space, which can be a problem if you don&amp;rsquo;t have a lot of available storage.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
