<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Computer Troubleshooting on Anikah Fauzia</title>
    <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/tags/computer-troubleshooting/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Computer Troubleshooting on Anikah Fauzia</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/tags/computer-troubleshooting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>This One Weird Trick Will Solve Your Error 0x0000011b on Windows 8 Instantly!</title>
      <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/this-one-weird-trick-will-solve-your-error-0x0000011b-on-windows-8-instantly-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/this-one-weird-trick-will-solve-your-error-0x0000011b-on-windows-8-instantly-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you facing Error 0x0000011b on Windows 8? If yes, you are not alone. This error can be quite frustrating and can prevent you from performing your tasks on the computer. In this blog post, we will discuss the causes of Error 0x0000011b on Windows 8 and the solutions to fix the issue.
Causes of Error 0x0000011b Error 0x0000011b can be caused by a number of factors. The most common causes are:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SOLVED: How to Fix Discord Ice Checking Stuck Issue in 5 Easy Steps!</title>
      <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/solved-how-to-fix-discord-ice-checking-stuck-issue-in-5-easy-steps-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/solved-how-to-fix-discord-ice-checking-stuck-issue-in-5-easy-steps-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you experiencing the Discord Ice Checking Stuck issue? Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, we have got you covered! In this blog post, we will discuss the Discord Ice Checking Stuck issue and provide you with five simple steps to fix it.
Definition of Discord Ice Checking Stuck Issue Discord Ice Checking Stuck is an issue that occurs when the Discord application is unable to connect to its servers. This can lead to Discord freezing, not responding, or crashing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Solve the Mystery: How to Fix a Disappearing Drive on Windows 10!</title>
      <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/solve-the-mystery-how-to-fix-a-disappearing-drive-on-windows-10-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/solve-the-mystery-how-to-fix-a-disappearing-drive-on-windows-10-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Have you ever experienced a disappearing drive on Windows 10? It can be a frustrating experience, especially when you don&amp;rsquo;t know what to do. In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll discuss what a disappearing drive is, the symptoms of a disappearing drive, the causes of a disappearing drive, and how to fix a disappearing drive.
Definition of a Disappearing Drive A disappearing drive is a drive that suddenly disappears from your computer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happens When Your Windows USB Isn&#39;t Recognized!</title>
      <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-your-windows-usb-isn-t-recognized-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-your-windows-usb-isn-t-recognized-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Have you ever experienced your Windows USB not being recognized? It can be a frustrating experience, but it doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to be. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explain what a Windows USB is, what signs to look out for when it isn&amp;rsquo;t being recognized, and the solutions to this problem.
Definition of Windows USB A Windows USB is a type of Universal Serial Bus (USB) that is used to connect devices to a Windows computer.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
