<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Internet Security on Anikah Fauzia</title>
    <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/tags/internet-security/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Internet Security on Anikah Fauzia</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/tags/internet-security/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Find Out if Fastboot is Really as Safe as They Say - You Might Be Surprised!</title>
      <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/find-out-if-fastboot-is-really-as-safe-as-they-say-you-might-be-surprised-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/find-out-if-fastboot-is-really-as-safe-as-they-say-you-might-be-surprised-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Fastboot is a popular method used to flash firmware onto Android devices. It is widely considered to be a secure and reliable way to update a device, but is it really? In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll take a look at the pros and cons of Fastboot to see if it really is as safe as they say.
Definition of Fastboot Fastboot is a tool that allows users to flash firmware onto their Android devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Simple Trick Will Help You Configure Proxy Internet in Minutes!</title>
      <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/this-simple-trick-will-help-you-configure-proxy-internet-in-minutes-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/this-simple-trick-will-help-you-configure-proxy-internet-in-minutes-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to Proxy Internet Proxy internet is a type of computer network that provides access to the internet through a proxy server. It allows users to access websites and services that are blocked by their local internet provider. Proxy internet is useful for bypassing geographical restrictions and censorship. It also helps protect users from malicious websites and hackers.
Benefits of Configuring Proxy Internet Configuring proxy internet can be beneficial for several reasons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happens When You See This Error Message: net::err_cert_authority_invalid</title>
      <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-see-this-error-message-net-err-cert-authority-invalid/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-see-this-error-message-net-err-cert-authority-invalid/</guid>
      <description>You Won&amp;rsquo;t Believe What Happens When You See This Error Message: net::err_cert_authority_invalid We&amp;rsquo;ve all been there. You&amp;rsquo;re trying to access a website, and then suddenly you see an error message that reads &amp;ldquo;net::err_cert_authority_invalid.&amp;rdquo; What does this mean? How can you fix it? In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the definition, causes, effects, and solutions to this error message.
I. Introduction A. Definition of error message
The net::err_cert_authority_invalid error message is an indication that the website you are trying to access has an invalid or expired SSL certificate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discover the Secret to Turning Off Safe Search - You Won&#39;t Believe How Easy It Is!</title>
      <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/discover-the-secret-to-turning-off-safe-search-you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/discover-the-secret-to-turning-off-safe-search-you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you tired of seeing filtered search results when you&amp;rsquo;re looking for something online? Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, you&amp;rsquo;re not alone. Many people are frustrated by the fact that their search results are being filtered by a safe search setting. Fortunately, it&amp;rsquo;s easy to turn off safe search and get the most accurate search results possible. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll discuss what safe search is, the benefits of turning it off, and how to do it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unlock the Secret to Unrestricted Access to the Best Torrent Sites with These Proxies!</title>
      <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/unlock-the-secret-to-unrestricted-access-to-the-best-torrent-sites-with-these-proxies-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/unlock-the-secret-to-unrestricted-access-to-the-best-torrent-sites-with-these-proxies-/</guid>
      <description>IV. Conclusion
Unlock the Secret to Unrestricted Access to the Best Torrent Sites with These Proxies! Torrenting is an excellent way to access files, movies, music, and more. But, sometimes, torrenting can be difficult due to restrictions put in place by ISPs or governments. To get around these restrictions, you can use a proxy server to access the best torrent sites. Proxies are a great way to unlock unrestricted access to the best torrent sites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happened When We Ran a DNS Probe and There Was No Internet!</title>
      <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-when-we-ran-a-dns-probe-and-there-was-no-internet-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-when-we-ran-a-dns-probe-and-there-was-no-internet-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction We all depend on the internet to stay connected and access the information we need. But what happens when the connection is lost? Recently, our team experienced this first-hand when we ran a DNS probe and there was no internet.
Definition of DNS Probe A DNS probe is a diagnostic tool used to identify potential problems with the Domain Name System (DNS). It is used to detect and troubleshoot DNS issues such as name resolution problems, slow response times, and other issues that can impact internet performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unlock the Secret to Surfing the Web Anonymously with Mode Incognito Chrome!</title>
      <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/unlock-the-secret-to-surfing-the-web-anonymously-with-mode-incognito-chrome-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/unlock-the-secret-to-surfing-the-web-anonymously-with-mode-incognito-chrome-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you looking for a way to surf the web anonymously? Incognito mode in Chrome is the perfect solution. Incognito mode is a private browsing mode that prevents your browsing history and activity from being tracked and stored. In this blog post, we’ll explain what incognito mode is and the benefits of using it, as well as how to activate it and tips for maximum anonymity.
Definition of Incognito Mode Incognito mode is a private browsing mode that prevents your browsing history and activity from being tracked and stored.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
