<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Windows 10 on Anikah Fauzia</title>
    <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/tags/windows-10/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Windows 10 on Anikah Fauzia</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/tags/windows-10/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Unbelievable! Discover How to Easily Recover Deleted Files in Windows 10 - Absolutely FREE!</title>
      <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/unbelievable-discover-how-to-easily-recover-deleted-files-in-windows-10-absolutely-free-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/unbelievable-discover-how-to-easily-recover-deleted-files-in-windows-10-absolutely-free-/</guid>
      <description>Unbelievable! Discover How to Easily Recover Deleted Files in Windows 10 - Absolutely FREE! Have you ever accidentally deleted an important file from your computer and thought there was no way to get it back? Well, don&amp;rsquo;t worry! There is an easy and free way to recover deleted files in Windows 10.
Introduction Deleted files are files that have been removed from the computer&amp;rsquo;s hard drive. They are not permanently erased from the computer, but rather stored in a special folder called the Recycle Bin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unlock the Power of File History and Make Windows 10 Backup a Breeze!</title>
      <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/unlock-the-power-of-file-history-and-make-windows-10-backup-a-breeze-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/unlock-the-power-of-file-history-and-make-windows-10-backup-a-breeze-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to File History Windows 10 File History is a powerful tool that makes backing up your files and data a breeze. It&amp;rsquo;s a feature that allows you to easily and quickly create a backup of your important files and folders. It is designed to help you keep your data safe, secure, and accessible.
What is File History? File History is a Windows 10 feature that allows you to back up your files and data to an external drive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happens When You Use VSSAdmin to Create a Windows 10 System!</title>
      <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-use-vssadmin-to-create-a-windows-10-system-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-use-vssadmin-to-create-a-windows-10-system-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you looking for an easy way to create a Windows 10 system? VSSAdmin is a powerful tool that can help you do just that. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll discuss what VSSAdmin is, the benefits of using it to create a Windows 10 system, and how to use it. Let&amp;rsquo;s dive in!
What is VSSAdmin? VSSAdmin is a command-line utility that is used to manage Volume Shadow Copies (VSCs).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dreaded Error 0x0000011b Strikes Again - How to Fix It in Windows 10</title>
      <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/dreaded-error-0x0000011b-strikes-again-how-to-fix-it-in-windows-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/dreaded-error-0x0000011b-strikes-again-how-to-fix-it-in-windows-10/</guid>
      <description>E. Run DISMIV. Conclusion
Introduction We’ve all been there - you’re working on something important and suddenly your computer starts acting up. You’re presented with the dreaded error 0x0000011b and you have no idea what to do. Don’t worry, we’ve got you covered. In this blog post, we’ll explain what error 0x0000011b is, how it affects Windows 10, and how you can fix it.
What is Error 0x0000011b? Error 0x0000011b is an error code that is displayed when there is a problem with a device driver or system file.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unlock the Secret to Super-Fast Internet Speeds with These Windows 10 QoS Settings Registry Hacks!</title>
      <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/unlock-the-secret-to-super-fast-internet-speeds-with-these-windows-10-qos-settings-registry-hacks-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/unlock-the-secret-to-super-fast-internet-speeds-with-these-windows-10-qos-settings-registry-hacks-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you looking to unlock the secret to super-fast internet speeds? Quality of Service (QoS) settings can help you do just that. QoS is a set of rules that prioritize certain types of internet traffic over others. By setting up QoS rules, you can ensure that your most important internet activities get the maximum speed and reliability. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll discuss the Windows 10 QoS settings registry hacks that can help you maximize your internet speeds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Solve the Mystery: How to Fix a Disappearing Drive on Windows 10!</title>
      <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/solve-the-mystery-how-to-fix-a-disappearing-drive-on-windows-10-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/solve-the-mystery-how-to-fix-a-disappearing-drive-on-windows-10-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Have you ever experienced a disappearing drive on Windows 10? It can be a frustrating experience, especially when you don&amp;rsquo;t know what to do. In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll discuss what a disappearing drive is, the symptoms of a disappearing drive, the causes of a disappearing drive, and how to fix a disappearing drive.
Definition of a Disappearing Drive A disappearing drive is a drive that suddenly disappears from your computer.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
