<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Game Development on Anikah Fauzia</title>
    <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/tags/game-development/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Game Development on Anikah Fauzia</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/tags/game-development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Unlock the Full Potential of Windows 10 with DirectX 12!</title>
      <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/unlock-the-full-potential-of-windows-10-with-directx-12-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/unlock-the-full-potential-of-windows-10-with-directx-12-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Windows 10 is the latest operating system from Microsoft and it comes with the latest version of DirectX 12. DirectX 12 is a powerful set of tools that help developers create immersive gaming experiences and enhance the performance of Windows 10. With DirectX 12, developers can take advantage of new features such as multi-threaded rendering and improved resource management to create stunning visuals and seamless gameplay.
Benefits of DirectX 12 DirectX 12 offers a wide range of benefits for Windows 10 users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe the Issues Fortnite is Having With Graphics Drivers - Here&#39;s What You Need to Know!</title>
      <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/you-won-t-believe-the-issues-fortnite-is-having-with-graphics-drivers-here-s-what-you-need-to-know-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/you-won-t-believe-the-issues-fortnite-is-having-with-graphics-drivers-here-s-what-you-need-to-know-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Fortnite is one of the most popular video games in the world. It has millions of players and is constantly being updated with new content. Unfortunately, some players are experiencing issues with their graphics drivers, leading to poor performance and other issues. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll take a look at the issues Fortnite is having with graphics drivers and what you can do to fix them.
Overview of Fortnite Fortnite is a battle royale game developed by Epic Games.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
