<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Games on Anikah Fauzia</title>
    <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/tags/games/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Games on Anikah Fauzia</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/tags/games/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Discover Amazing Apps and Games in the Windows App Store!</title>
      <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/discover-amazing-apps-and-games-in-the-windows-app-store-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/discover-amazing-apps-and-games-in-the-windows-app-store-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to the Windows App Store The Windows App Store is an online marketplace where users can discover and download a variety of apps and games for their Windows device. With a wide selection of both free and paid apps and games, the Windows App Store provides users with an easy and convenient way to access the content they need.
What is the Windows App Store? The Windows App Store is a digital distribution platform for Windows devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What You Can Find in the Windows Store URI List!</title>
      <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-you-can-find-in-the-windows-store-uri-list-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/techno/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-you-can-find-in-the-windows-store-uri-list-/</guid>
      <description>You Won&amp;rsquo;t Believe What You Can Find in the Windows Store URI List! Are you looking for a way to access the Windows Store? Do you want to find out what types of URIs are available in the Windows Store? Look no further! In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll be exploring the Windows Store URI List and the benefits of using it.
Introduction Overview of Windows Store URI List The Windows Store URI List is a list of Uniform Resource Identifiers (URIs) that can be used to access the Windows Store.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
